Bhrugu Tundeliya

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/bhrugu-tundeliya

Github: https://github.com/Bhrugu14

StackOverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/7034453/bhrugu-tundeliya

115/16 Shyamtenament Manjipura Road, Nadiad 387001

(91) 8460304001

☑ bhrugu1409@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A passionate professional and a fast learner; years of working experience of software design principles and agile development principles. worked independently as well as in a team for projects. Having experience in mobile and web development

EXPERIENCE

Technostacks Infotech Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad — *Software Developer*

July 2022 - PRESENT

Codentic software, Anand — *React Developer*

October 2020 - June 2022

PROJECTS

Grocery Application— react native, typescript

Responsible for creating user and delivery partner's application from the scratch, Implemented Family mode that handles group purchase, implemented Razorpay API

Catalog Application (Mobile and Website) — Next.js, nodejs, React Native

Build a Mobile responsive website for product catalog with a modern eye-catching design. Working with the remote backend team for development. Integrated MirrAR Ar web plug-in for the try-on feature.

E-commerce sweets selling website — *Next.js, nodejs*

Responsible for bug fixes and design changes on the already developed website, rework on payment module with different payment methods and promo code integration.

BLE Connector — *React Native, Typescript*

Created a Mobile application that can detect certain service UUID and connect to it, send and receive messages via BLE.

Online Documents Storage — React js, Ionic

Responsible for client communication information gathering, design, and development of the project, managed role-based scenario in folder options, implemented reminder feature with different kinds ranges.

Rewards-Driven Application — *React Native*

Independently designed and developed the Front end of a mobile application, that detects users in close promxemtery of the vendor's application with Socket, Vendor can send customer-related offers with that. implemented one-signal for notification

Online Menu, Promo QRCode generation, Club Application—

React Native, Next js

worked on an online menu project that gets dynamic URLs from QRcode, generates Lottery QRcode with vendor's admin panel, and also bug fixes on clubbing Application for Germany.

SKILLS

- React
- Next
- lonic
- React Native
- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- Redux
- Mobx
- Typescript
- Vue(basic)
- Android(basic)
- Nodejs(basic)
- Express(basic)

TOOLS

- Vscode
- Android Studio
- Xcode

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

EDUCATION

Birla Vishvakarma Mahavidhyalaya(BVM), Anand — Computer Engineering — July 2013 - December 2020.